Just like in the email we saw between Allen and Steve.
就像我们在艾伦和史蒂夫之间看到的电子邮件一样。
The sentence at the very end can serve as a little push and I want to go through just a couple more
最后的那句话可以起到一点推动作用，我想再讲几句
of sentences like that.
之类的句子。
There are many many more possible sentences something you can put at the end to just offer a tiny nudge
还有更多可能的句子，你可以放在最后，只是稍微推动一下
or maybe add a little extra information.
或者添加一些额外的信息。
Sometimes can be used to make a comment like I hope your parents are doing OK that's fine too.
有时可以用来发表评论，比如我希望你父母一切都好，这也很好。
OK but this is for a professional email.
好的，但这是一个专业的电子邮件。
Looking forward to hearing from you.
期待您的回音。
Please let me know A.S.A.P. as soon as possible.
请让我知道 A.S.A.P.尽早。
Let me know if you have any questions let me know if you have any questions send me these by Friday
让我知道如果您有任何问题让我知道如果您有任何问题在星期五之前将这些发送给我
if you can send me these by Friday if you can.
如果可以的话，你能在星期五之前把这些寄给我吗？
Or please send me these by Friday if you can.
或者如果可以的话，请在星期五之前把这些寄给我。
I'll follow up next week.
下周我会跟进。
That means I will contact you next week to make sure that what we discussed in this e-mail is happening.
这意味着我将在下周与您联系，以确保我们在这封电子邮件中讨论的内容正在发生。
I'm going to make sure that everything is on track.
我将确保一切正常。
Keep me up to speed.
让我跟上进度。
That means if something changes let me know.
这意味着如果有什么变化让我知道。
That basically means Keep me updated Keep me updated keep me up to date keep me up to speed.
这基本上意味着让我更新让我更新让我保持最新让我跟上速度。
Same thing sometimes we say keep me also in the loop in the loop is very common.
同样的事情有时我们说让我也在循环中循环是很常见的。
Make sure to keep me in the loop keep me up to speed.
确保让我了解最新情况，让我跟上进度。
Keep me up to date.
让我了解最新情况。
These are all very very common.
这些都是非常非常常见的。
OK.
好的。
And that really means send me updates when things change when things happen.
这实际上意味着当事情发生变化时向我发送更新。
I need to know.
我需要知道。
OK.
好的。
These are more professional ones.
这些是更专业的。
These are for more professional e-mails.
这些用于更专业的电子邮件。
Then for more friendly ones we might say things like I hope everything is really good with your family.
然后对于更友好的人，我们可能会说我希望你的家人一切都好。
A comment or a small question but I want to make sure you feel comfortable using these because they're
一个评论或一个小问题，但我想确保您对使用这些感到自在，因为它们是
very common for professional emails.
对于专业电子邮件非常常见。
So we've gone through our tips for e-mails we've gone through examples of formal and informal emails.
所以我们已经浏览了我们的电子邮件提示，我们浏览了正式和非正式电子邮件的示例。
The last thing I want to do very quickly is just go over some things that are said at the end of an
我想做的最后一件事就是回顾一下在结束时所说的一些事情
email right before you write your name followed by a comma followed by a comma.
在您写下您的姓名之前发送电子邮件，然后是逗号，然后是逗号。
These aren't all of them.
这些还不是全部。
There are many many more I just want to give you a feeling for which ones are neutral which ones are
还有很多很多我只是想让你感觉一下哪些是中性的，哪些是中性的
very professional formal which ones are very friendly.
非常专业的正式，非常友好。
OK.
好的。
Take care.
小心。
But I should start with these two regards.
但我应该从这两个方面开始。
Best regards.
此致。
OK.
好的。
This is pretty general use.
这是相当普遍的用途。
Very let's say General or neutral.
非常让我们说一般或中立。
You could use it in a professional situation.
您可以在专业情况下使用它。
You could use it with a friend could use it with a teacher.
你可以和朋友一起使用，也可以和老师一起使用。
Very useful.
很有用。
Take care.
小心。
This is probably more personal sincerely.
这可能是更个人的真诚。
Could be could be neutral but it's often more personal.
可以是中性的，但通常更个人化。
So it depends on the situation.
所以要视情况而定。
Yours truly is definitely personal.
你的绝对是个人的。
Very personal.
很有个性。
Cheers.
干杯。
Could be pretty neutral could be pretty neutral so cheers is often for maybe a colleague a co-worker
可能相当中立 可能相当中立 所以欢呼通常是为同事或同事
or if you're writing a quick e-mail to somebody you maybe are in touch with regularly.
或者，如果您正在给您可能经常联系的人写一封快速电子邮件。
Thanks is pretty general pretty general pretty neutral.
谢谢是很一般很一般很中性。
You could use that one.
你可以用那个。
This is very personal.
这是非常个人的。
Love is very personal.
爱是非常个人化的。
Take it easy is let's say very friendly but you could use it in a professional situation if you need
放轻松，让我们说非常友好，但如果需要，您可以在专业情况下使用它
to.
至。
It's very friendly but very relaxed.
它非常友好但非常放松。
It's not too formal but you could use it professionally.
它不是太正式，但你可以专业地使用它。
Have a good one is the same as take it easy.
拥有一个好人就等于放轻松。
It's pretty friendly but could be used neutrally for a friend or for a colleague or a co-worker later
它非常友好，但以后可以中立地用于朋友或同事或同事
is definitely very casual very casual very relaxed you wouldn't probably use that with a colleague unless
绝对是非常随意 非常随意 非常放松 你可能不会和同事一起使用它，除非
you knew them really really well and see you is not really used that often in e-mail.
您非常了解它们，并且看到您在电子邮件中并不经常使用。
It might be used just as a text message or a message to a friend but see you is often pretty personal
它可能只是用作短信或给朋友的信息，但看到你通常很私人
pretty personal.
很个人。
I just wanted to give you a quick feeling for them and some examples.
我只是想给你一个快速的感觉和一些例子。
There are many many more I would recommend just looking them up on the Internet finding a list and looking
还有更多我建议您在互联网上查找列表并查找
at some examples maybe of emails to see how they're used.
在某些示例中，可能是电子邮件，以了解它们的使用方式。
Of course the best way to get good at something is to practice it.
当然，擅长某事的最好方法是实践它。
So what I'd like you to do is practice writing either a business or formal email review it carefully
所以我想让你做的是练习写商业或正式的电子邮件仔细审查它
to ensure that tone and style fit your purpose.
以确保语气和风格符合您的目的。
Make sure it fits the purpose and also make sure that your punctuation is perfect.
确保它符合目的，并确保你的标点符号是完美的。
It's got to be perfect.
它必须是完美的。
Try a few.
尝试几个。
Write a personal one and a professional one.
写个人的和专业的。
If you have time get feedback from people you know send it to a friend.
如果您有时间从认识的人那里获得反馈，请将其发送给朋友。
Have them look at it for you.
让他们帮你看看。
And as I mentioned use something like grammar Lee to check your punctuation check your spelling and
正如我提到的，使用语法 Lee 之类的东西来检查你的标点符号 检查你的拼写和
check your basic grammar.
检查你的基本语法。
OK.
好的。
Good luck.
祝你好运。